

# Contact

+66 97 063 2416 Skype: live:alax54321 alax54321@gmail.com http://linkedin.com/in/alaxaung-kyaw-kyaw-0115081b9 https://facebook.com/24625067 20550752

# Specialization & Skills

**Software Engineering:** Mobile Engineer, Frontend Engineer, System Engineer

Javascript (1 year), HTML5 (1 year), CSS (1 year), React (< 1 years), JQuery (1 year)

# Languages

English - Advanced Thai - Proficient Spanish - Beginner Burmese - Native

# **Aung Kyaw Kyaw Alax**

# Mobile Engineer, Frontend Engineer, System Engineer

Pangkok, Thailand

Date of birth: September 1st 1996 (25 years old)

A highly motivated Front-End Developer with proven abilities to collaborate efficiently with senior developers. Eager to working closely with team members with enthusiasms to build and deliver dynamic solutions. Passionate and intensive to forge prominent solutions to people and community with an objective to form the world a better liveable place. With driven goals, I have attended hundreds of hours of coding courses and workshops to sharpen my skills while perfecting my personal growth and existed skillsets. Excitedly ready to be connected my passion as a significant jigsaw to talented tech team to complete great mission puzzles.

# **Work Experience**

# Expatriate Liaison Officer

Bumrungrad International Hospital - Full-time

Middle, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

• Coordinated and liaised for expat patients with various departments with their procedure and providing information and supports. • Advocated proactively patients with hospital facilities and environments as required. • Responded and handled inquiries of patients received via emails, phone calls and walk-ins by using tools and software like Intersystems TrakCare, Microsoft Office apps. • Contributed with communications, explanations and interpretations with healthcare providers in Thai, Burmese, English languages. • Studied patients' feedbacks and perform service enhancement/recovery systematically with related department. • Professionally assisted VIP/ High-class patients with their appointments, procedures and escorted according to schedules. • Worked and supported closely with business development team to enhance expat market.

### Inter Ops Officer (Myanmar Patient Liaison)

Bumrungrad International Hospital - Full-time

Middle, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

Sep 2018 - Oct 2020 2 years 1 month

Nov 2020 - Present

1 year 7 months

- Mainly performed interpretations in live or remote with conversations between healthcare providers and Myanmar patients. Coordinated various inquiries and arranged appointments before or during their visits to hospital. Provided information and discussions and with their diagnosis and treatment plans. Visited admitted patients to ensure conveniences and provided supports as required. Showed culture and tradition awareness in manners, apparels and gestures to Myanmar patients. Escorted and assisted patients carefully during their appointments as required. Used software and tools as Intersystems TrakCare, Microsoft Office apps in handling inquiries, visits, inpatients' censuses. Work closely and support with Marketing team and Patient Experience team to enhance Myanmar market.
- Freelance Interpreter/ Translator

N/A - Freelance Jan 2017 - Aug 2018

Entry, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

Meeting and Greeting the patients upon the appointments. Verify patients' demographics and confirming the processes of the procedure according to appointments. Escort patients carefully during procedure as necessary. Interpret the whole conversations regarding diagnosis and treatment plans between doctors and patients vice versa accurately. Give productive assistance to patients' health journeys based on doctor opinions and treatment plans, thoroughly. Coordinate with every related departments and teams arrange reservations, schedules and future appointments as required. Create daily productivities report and set remarks and alerts for follow up process in future.

# **Education**

# University of Greenwich

Business Information Technology, Computer Science and Information Sciences and Support Services

2017 - 2018

1 year 7 months

KMD Institute

Information Technology

2014 - 2015

NCC Education Level-5 Diploma in Computing (QCF)

University of Greenwich

2018

KMD Institute

2015

# **Licenses & Certifications**

#### **Responsive Web Design**

freeCodeCamp

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### JAVASCRIPT COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued November 2021 - No Expiration Date

# HTML FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued January 2020 - No Expiration Date

# **CSS FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION**

Sololearn

Issued February 2020 - No Expiration Date

### **Responsive Web Design Course**

Sololearn

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### **jQuery Course Completion**

Sololearn

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### Responsive Web Design

# freeCodeCamp

Issued January 2022

#### JAVASCRIPT COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued November 2021

#### HTML FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued January 2020

#### **CSS FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION**

Sololearn

Issued February 2020

# **Responsive Web Design Course**

Sololearn

Issued January 2022

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued April 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### **Award**

# On the Spot Rewards

Senior Manager - Customer Advocate (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

November 2021

• Have Agility & Caring as key attributes in handling patients

# On the Spot Rewards

Day Executive Officer - Hospital Duty (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

March 2021

• Effective coordination with team in taking care demanding patient. • Self-learning and quick understanding in patient's situation. • Empathy and helpful to make customer satisfaction.

### On the Spot Rewards

Coordination Physician - Medical Coordination (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

September 2020

· Worked proactively for Bumrungrad Relief Flight project.

# On the Spot Rewards

Associate Division Director - Clinical Operations (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

October 2019

• Excellence works in caring patients, live interpreting/ translating. • Bumrungrad International way (ways of performance) excellence.

# On the Spot Rewards

Senior Nurse Manager - Health Screening & Genomics (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

August 2018

• Very patience in listening to patients, good service, professional.

